

D 1 (M

Product Manager

Gurman Singh

CONTACT



1 (226) 980-9134 Phone Number gsing994@gmail.com Email www.GurmanSingh.com

EDUCATION

Bachelor of Science (Hons) Concentration: Genetic Engineering

Website

The University of Western Ontario

SKILLS

PROCESS MANAGEMENT

SaaS & IaaS BASIC ARCHITECTURE

MARKETING STRATEGY

DIGITAL ADVERTISING

MOBILE MARKETING

WEBSITE DESIGN/HTML



SUMMARY

An accomplished product management professional with five years of bringing products to market. Experienced in strategy and leading large product releases to drive over 300 million downloads and 250 million monthly impressions. Highly organized, detail-oriented, and conscientious self-starter, able to strategize and prioritize effectively to accomplish multiple tasks with creativity, enthusiasm and humor.

PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE



Advanced Micro Devices (AMD) - Product Manager

May 2018 - Present

- Received the AMD Next 5% Award for the release of 2 new innovative Radeon RX 5700 series features (Radeon Anti-Lag and Radeon Image Sharpening)
- Received an executive spotlight award for directing the launch of Radeon Software Adrenalin 2019
- Identified and prioritized software features required to meet new product performance goals
- Defined and drove Radeon Software performance plan for new products
- Acquired technical knowledge to work with engineering and execution teams
- Continuously drove the coordination of ISV engineering, performance engineering, driver development teams and technical marketing lab



Advanced Micro Devices (AMD) – Product Marketing Specialist

June 2016 - May 2018

- Received a director's spotlight award for marketing a 2017 software launch
- Lead five product and software launches gathering over 1 billion total impressions
- Developed technical and highlevel storytelling for Radeon products
- Conducted campaign analyses to develop company-wide KPIs which anticipate industry trends and provide recommendations for product features
- Created marketing content for sales enablement, marketing newsletters and other customer viewable web content



The University of Western Ontario - Microsoft Account Specialist

January 2015 - May 2016

- Built long term partnerships with customers to enable continued value of Microsoft products
- Drove the adoption of Microsoft platform services through various channel driven activations
- Recognized as a product expert and educated customers on various Microsoft solutions
- Provided products which promoted the integration of accessibility with technology
- Ensured customer value through defining and achieving business outcomes